A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Diabetes, Therapy (Phenformin) - DBI 'Tuned Disintegration'" 4:40, Issue 87, 1962 May 11 (Box 36, Folder 7-9)
- [Hypertension for Issue #89 is with Issue #86] (Box 36, Folder 10)
- "Estrogens-Drugs in the Movement of Puerperal Breast Engorgement" 4:41, Issue 88, 1962 May 25 (Box 37, Folder 1-3)
- "Vitamins C-Vitamin C Prophylaxis in Surgery and Serious Injury" 4:42, Issue 88, 1962 May 25 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- "Liver Disease-Immunization of Travelers Against Infectious Hepatitis" 4:43, Issue 88, 1962 May 25 (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
- "Hydroxyphenamate-Listica" 4:45, Issue 89, 1962 June 8 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- "Narcotics-Dosage and Cost of Narcotic Drugs" 4:45, Issue 89, 1962 June 8 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- "Cymotrypsin-Avazyme" 4:49, Issue 90, 1962 June 22 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
- "Pre-Anesthetic Medication-Pre-Anesthetic Medication" 4:50, Issue 90, 1962 June 22 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- "Sulfonamides-Gantanol" 4:53, Issue 91, 1962 July 6 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
- "Contraceptives, Oral-Oral Contraceptives" 4:54, Issue 91, 1962 July 6 (Box 38, Folder 6-8)
- "Anticonvulsants-Lymphoma Syndrome Induced by Anticonvulsants" 4:56, Issue 91, 1962 July 6 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
- "Antimicrobials, Combination-Novobiocin & Panalba" 4:57, Issue 92, 1962 July 20 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
- "Oxygen-Emergency Oxygen Outside the Hospital" 4:58, Issue 92, 1962 July 20 (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
- "Oxygen-Portable Oxygen Equipment" 4:62, Issue 93, 1962 August 3 (Box 39, Folder 5-7)
- "Glutethimide-Doriden" 4:61, Issue 93, 1962 August 3 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
- "Lipids-Chole-tech Serum Cholesterol Kit" 4:64, Issue 93, 1962 August 3 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- "Phenothiazines (Thioridazine) - Mellaril" 4:65, Issue 94, 1962 August 17 (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
- "Methoxyflurane-Penthrane" 4:67, Issue 94, 1962 August 17 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- "Tuberculin-Tuberculin Skin Tests" 4:67, Issue 94, 1962 August 17 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
- "Methysergide-Sansert" 4:70, Issue 95, 1962 August 31 (Box 40, Folder 9-11)
- "Premarin and Coronary Artery Disease" 5:1, Issue 104, 1963 January 4 (Box 41, Folder 1-8)
- "Hypertensin" 5:3, Issue 104, 1963 January 4 (Box 41, Folder 9-10)
- "Gelatin and Fragile Fingernails" 5:4, Issue 104, 1963 January 4 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- "Kanamycin" 5:5, Issue 105, 1963 January 18 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
- "S-26 - - A New Infant Milk Preparation" 5:8, Issue 105, 1963 January 18 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- "Tuss-Ornade and Cold Remedies" 5:11, Issue 106, 1963 February 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- "Aldomet" 5:13, Issue 106, 1963 February 1; 1 of 3 (Box 42, Folder 6-8)
- "Reassessment of Coly-Mycin" 5:15, Issue 107, 1963 February 15; 1 of 4 (Box 42, Folder 9-12)
- "The Coice of Systemic Antimicrobial Agents" 5:17, Issue 108, 1963 March 1 (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
- "The Treatment of Leukemia" 5:21, Issue 109, 1963 March 15 (Box 43, Folder 5-7)
- "Hemastix" 5:24, Issue 109, 1963 March 15 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- "Tepanil, Tenuate, and Other Appetite-Depressing Drugs" 5:25, Issue 110, 1963 March 29 (Box 43, Folder 9-11)
- "Trepidone" 5:29, Issue 111, 1963 April 12 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- "Furadantin, Oral and Intravenous" 5:30, Issue 111, 1963 April 12 (Box 44, Folder 2-5)
- "Goiter Caused by Iodides, Cobalt and Antithyroid Drugs" 5:31, Issue 111, 1963 April 12 (Box 44, Folder 6-8)
- "Flagyl, a Systemic Trichomonacide" 5:33, Issue 112, 1963 April 26 (Box 44, Folder 9-12)
- "Ortho-Novum, Enovid and Thromboembolic Disease" 5:34, Issue 112, 1963 April 26 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
- "Measles Vaccines" 5:35, Issue 112, 1963 April 26 (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
- "Oral Antidiabetic Agents in Pregnancy" 5:39, Issue 113, 1963 May 10 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- "Entonyl and MAO Inhibitors" 5:40, Issue 114, 1963 May 24 (Box 45, Folder 6-9)
- "Fluothane" 5:44, Issue 114, 1963 May 24 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- "Old Drugs - New Hazards, III. Orabilex and Renal Disease" 5:47, Issue 115, 1963 June 7 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- "Old Drugs - New Hazards, IV. Topical Ophthalmic Steroids and Glaucoma" 5:47, Issue 115, 1963 June 7 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- "Antivert and Meniere's Syndrome" 5:49, Issue 116, 1963 June 21 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- "Chloramphenicol and Urinary Tract Infections" 5:50, Issue 116, 1963 June 21 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- "The Narcotic Antagonists" 5:51, Issue 116, 1963 June 21 (Box 46, Folder 2-4)
- "Methenamine Mandelate and Urinary Tract Infections" 5:53, Issue 117, 1963 July 5 (Box 46, Folder 5-8)
- "Alphalac" 5:54, Issue 117, 1963 July 5 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- "Another 'Anti-Cancer' Drug: Laetrile" 5:55, Issue 117, 1963 July 5 (Box 46, Folder 10-11)
- "References Used in Drug Advertisements" 5:56, Issue 117, 1963 July 5 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- "Anti-infective Agents in the Treatment of Diarrhea" 5:57, Issue 118, 1963 July 19 (Box 47, Folder 2-6)
- "Symptomatic Treatment of Diarrhea" 5:61, Issue 119, August 2, 1963 & "A Note on Treatment of Severe Diarrhea" 5:80, Issue 123, September 27, 1963, 1963 August 2 1963 September 27 (Box 47, Folder 7-8)
- "Gall Bladder and Bile Duct Contrast Media" 5:67, Issue 120, 1963 August 16 (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
- "Meprobamate Addiction and Deprol" 5:71, Issue 121, 1963 August 30 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- "Calcium, Steroids and Osteoporosis" 5:73, Issue 122, 1963 September 13 (Box 48, Folder 1-4)
- "Ritalin" 5:75, Issue 122, 1963 September 13 (Box 48, Folder 5-8)
- "Surgery and Drugs in the Treatment of Mammary Cancer" 5:77, Issue 123, 1963 September 27 (Box 48, Folder 9-11)
- "Soma and Soma Compound" 5:79, Issue 123, 1963 September 27 (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
- "Drugs Which Lower the Blood Lipids" 5:81, Issue 124, 1963 October 11 (Box 49, Folder 4-8)
- "Beta-Chlor and Chloral Hydrate" 5:83, Issue 124, 1963 October 11 (Box 49, Folder 9-10)
- "Antibiotic Prophylaxis in Chronic Bronchitis" 5:85, Issue 125, 1963 October 25; 1 of 2 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- "Antibiotic Prophylaxis in Chronic Bronchitis" 5:85, Issue 125, 1963 October 25; 2 of 2 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- "Librium" 5:93, Issue 127, 1963 November 22 (Box 50, Folder 2-5)
- "Tests of Chloral Hydrate" 5:94, Issue 127, 1963 November 22 (Box 50, Folder 6-8)
- "Steroid Aerosols and Bronchial Asthma" 5:99, Issue 128, 1963 December 6 (Box 50, Folder 9-11)
- "Intermittent Positive Pressure Breathing Devices" 5:100, Issue 128, 1963 December 6 (Box 51, Folder 1-4)
- "Antibiotics for Hemophilus Influenzae Infections" 5:101, Issue 129, 1963 December 20 (Box 51, Folder 5-7)
- "Amphocortrin and Other Topical Antibacterial Products" 6:3, Issue 130, 1964 January 3 (Box 51, Folder 8-10)
- "Erythromycin and Triacetyloleandomycin" 6:5, Issue 131, 1964 January 17 (Box 51, Folder 11, Box 52, Folder 1-2)
- "Skelaxin" 6:6, Issue 131, 1964 January 17 (Box 52, Folder 3-4)
- "Diet, Serum Lipids and Atherosclerosis" 6:9, Issue 132, 1964 January 31 (Box 52, Folder 5-7)
- "Topical Treatment of Chronic Simple Glaucoma" 6:10, Issue 132, 1964 January 31 (Box 52, Folder 8-10)
- "Capla and the Treatment of Hypertension" 6:12, Issue 132, 1964 January 31 (Box 52, Folder 11, Box 53, Folder 1)
- "Steri-strip and Steri-drape" 6:15, Issue 133, 1964 February 14 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- "Orabilex" 6:16, Issue 133, 1964 February 14 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- "Tests of Heparin Preparations" 6:20, Issue 134, 1964 February 28 (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
- "Emprazil-C Tablets and Shotgun Therapy" 6:24, Issue 135, 1964 March 13 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- "Low-Dosage Topical Steroids" 6:27, Issue 136, 1964 March 27 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- "Cyclospasmol, Vasodilan and Arlidin in Cerebrovascular Disease" 6:27, Issue 136, 1964 March 27 (Box 53, Folder 8-10)
- "Nafcillin (Unipen) " 6:29, Issue 137, 1964 April 10 (Box 53, Folder 11-12, Box 54, Folder 1-2)
- "Acetohexamide (Dymelor) " 6:31, Issue 137, 1964 April 10 (Box 54, Folder 3-6)
- "Heparin - A Correction" 6:32, Issue 137, 1964 April 10 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- "Ictotest and Infectious Hepatitis" 6:39, Issue 139, 1964 May 8 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- "Darvon" 6:41, Issue 140, May 22, 1964; "Darvon - A Correction" 6:56, Issue 143, July 3, 1964, 1964 May 22; 1964 July 3 (Box 54, Folder 9-11)
- "The Codeine Group of Drugs" 6:42, Issue 140, 1964 May 22 (Box 54, Folder 12-13, Box 55, Folder 1-2)
- "Mammography: Some Reservations" 6:43, Issue 140, 1964 May 22 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- "Aldoril and Methyldopa" 6:47, Issue 141, 1964 June 5 (Box 55, Folder 4-6)
- "Partial Throboplastin Time and 'Thrombofax'" 6:48, Issue 141, 1964 June 5 (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
- "Oral Iron Therapy" 6:49, Issue 142, 1964 June 19 (Box 55, Folder 9-11, Box 56, Folder 1-2)
- "Neo-Barine" 6:50, Issue 142, 1964 June 19 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- "The Safety of Drugs for Intravenous Pyelography" 6:55, Issue 143, 1964 July 3 (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
- "NegGram" 6:57, Issue 144, 1964 July 17 (Box 56, Folder 6-9)
- "New Oral Contraceptives" 6:59, Issue 144, 1964 July 17 (Box 56, Folder 10-11, Box 57, Folder 1-2)
- "Perfron First-Aid Pads" 6:60, Issue 144, 1964 July 17 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- "Intrauterine Devices and Other New Contraceptive Materials" 6:63, Issue 145, 1964 July 31 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
- "Androgenic Hormones in Anemia" 6:65, Issue 146, 1964 August 14 (Box 57, Folder 6-9)
- "Anticoagulants in Coronary Artery Disease" 6:69, Issue 147, 1964 August 28 (Box 57, Folder 10-11, Box 58, Folder 1-2)
- "Indoklon" 6:76, Issue 148, 1964 September 11 (Box 58, Folder 3-4)
- "Penicillin Allergy" 6:77, Issue 149, 1964 September 25 (Box 58, Folder 5-7)
- "Which Penicillin?" 6:81, Issue 150, 1964 October 9 (Box 58, Folder 8-10)
- "Kanamycin" Pre-Publication Issue, 1958 December (Box 59, Folder 1)
- "Diuril" Pre-Publication Issue, 1958 December (Box 59, Folder 2)
- "Demerol vs. Morphine" Pre-Publication Issue, 1958 December (Box 59, Folder 3)
- "Geritol" Pre-Publication Issue, 1958 December (Box 59, Folder 4)
- "Meprolone" unpublished, 1959 February (Box 59, Folder 5)
- "Diabinese" 1:13, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- "Neutrapen" 1:13, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- "Oral Cold Remedies" 1:23, Issue 6, 1959 April 3 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- "Deafness Caused by Antibiotics" 1:29, Issue 8, 1959 May 1 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- "Diuril, Hydrodiuril and Esidrix" 1:33, Issue 9, 1959 May 15 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- "Syrosingopine (CIBA Correspondence) ", 1959 April-1960 February (Box 59, Folder 11-12)
- "Visine Eye Drops" unpublished, 1959 June (Box 59, Folder 13)
- "'Prolonged-Action' Drugs" 1:45, Issue 12, 1959 June 26 (Box 59, Folder 14-15)
- "Parenteral Drugs for Hypertensive Crises" unpublished, 1959 July (Box 59, Folder 16)
- "Carbonic Anhydrase Inhibitors" 1:62, Issue 16, 1959 August 21 (Box 59, Folder 17-18)
- "Autocoagulant Drugs" unpublished, 1959 September (Box 59, Folder 19)
- "DBI" 1:69, Issue 18, 1959 September 18 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
- "Ademol" 1:79, Issue 20, 1959 October 16 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- "Levonor" unpublished, 1959 October (Box 60, Folder 4)
- "Antimicrobial Chemoprophylaxis" 1:81, Issue 21, 1959 October 30 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- "The Safety and Effectiveness of New Drugs" unpublished, 1959 December (Box 60, Folder 6)
- "Saluron" 2:6, Issue 27, 1960 January 22 (Box 60, Folder 7-8)
- "Antibiotic Prophylaxis for Severe Traumatic Wounds" 2:15, Issue 29, 1960 February 19 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- "Chemotherapy of Malignant Lymphomas" 2:25, Issue 32, 1960 April 1 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- "Effect of Meals on Absorption of Oral Anti-infective Agents" 2:27, Issue 32, 1960 April 1 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- "Treatment of Trichomonal Vaginitis" 2:33, Issue 34, 1960 April 29 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- "Griseofulvin - A New Appraisal" 2:42, Issue 36, 1960 May 27 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- "A Note on Diabinese" 2:44, Issue 36, 1960 May 27 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- "Man-Tan and Other Chemical Skin-Tanning Preparations" 2:47, Issue 37, 1960 June 10 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- "Aldactone" 2:49, Issue 38, 1960 June 24 (Box 60, Folder 16-17, Box 61, Folder 1)
- "Humatin" 2:53, Issue 39, 1960 July 8 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- "Naturetin and Naqua" 2:57, Issue 40, 1960 July 22 (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
- "Antihistamines for Allergic Disorders" 2:59, Issue 40, 1960 July 22 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- "Colace and Other Wetting Agents for Constipation" 2:61, Issue 41, 1960 August 5 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- "Hygroton" 2:76, Issue 44, 1960 September 16 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- "Protamide" 2:80, Issue 45, 1960 September 30 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- "Elipten" 2:83, Issue 46, 1960 October 14 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- "Cough Remedies" 2:101, Issue 51, 1960 December 23 (Box 61, Folder 10-11)
- "Proteolic Enzymes as Anti-Inflammatory Agents" 3:11, Issue 54, 1961 February 3 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
- "Cotazym" 3:15, Issue 55, 1961 February 17 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- "Mercurial Diuretics" 3:17 Issue 56, 1961 March 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- "Cotazym - Correction" 3:32, Issue 59, 1961 April 14 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- "More Oral Thiazide Diuretics" 3:35, Issue 60, 1961 April 28 (Box 62, Folder 6-7)
- "Aminopyrine Nonprescription Drugs Abroad" 3:44, Issue 62, 1961 May 26 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- "Tests of Digitoxin Tablets" 3:47, Issue 63, 1961 June 9 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- "Pyridium" 3:55, Issue 65, 1961 July 7 (Box 62, Folder 10-11)
- "Tests of Digoxin Tablets" 3:92, Issue 64, 1961 November 10 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- "Key-Pyrone" 3:94, Issue 75, 1961 November 24 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- "Nisentil" 3:98, Issue 76, 1961 December 8 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- "MER/29 and Warnings on New Drugs" 4:5, Issue 79, 1962 January 19 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- "Renese" 4:12, Issue 80, 1962 February 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- "Tests of Diethylstilbestrol Tablets" 4:15, Issue 81, 1962 February 16 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- "Arginine and Other Agents for Hepatic Coma" 4:33, Issue 86, 1962 April 27 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- "Thalidomide and Other Hazardous Drugs" 4:47, Issue 89, 1962 June 8 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- "Air Conditioners, Filters, Purifiers and Ionizers" 4:50, Issue 90, 1962 June 22 (Box 63, Folder 8-12)
- "Ananase" 4:60, Issue 92, 1962 July 20 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
- "Drugs and Congenital Defects" 4:69, Issue 95, 1962 August 31 (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
- "Repository Antigens for Hay Fever" 4:72, Issue 95, 1962 August 31 (Box 64, Folder 6-7)
- "Duphaston: A New Progestogen" 4:73, Issue 96, 1970 January 26-October 2 (Box 64, Folder 8-9)
- "Injury by Phenindione Anticoagulants: 4:74, Issue 96, 1962 September 14 (Box 64, Folder 10-11)
- "Choice of Digitalis Drugs" 4:75, Issue 96, 1962 September 14 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
- "Novrad" 4:77, Issue 97, 1962 September 28 (Box 65, Folder 3-4)
- "Emivan and Other Analeptec Drugs" 4:78, Issue 97, 1962 September 28 (Box 65, Folder 5-6)
- "Influenza Vaccine" 4:79, Issue 97, 1962 September 28 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- "Poliomyelitis Vaccines" 4:81, Issue 98, 1962 October 12 (Box 65, Folder 8-9)
- "Adrenocortical Steroids in Cancer" 4:82, Issue 98, 1962 October 12 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- "Viomycin and Chemotherapy of Pulmonary Tuberculosis" 4:83, Issue 98, 1962 October 12 (Box 65, Folder 11-12, Box 66, Folder 1)
- "Taractan" 4:85, Issue 99, 1962 October 26 (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
- "Silent Springs" 4:86, Issue 99, 1962 October 26 (Box 66, Folder 4-10)
- "Atabrine, Aralen and Plaquenil" Unpublished (Box 66, Folder 11)
- "Doriden and Thalidomide" 4:88, Issue 99, 1962 October 26 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- "Combinations of Analgesics With Amphetamines" 4:89, Issue 100, 1962 November 9 (Box 67, Folder 1-3)
- "Surgical Masks and Wound Infections" 4:91, Issue 100, 1962 November 9 (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
- "Metapirone" 4:92, Issue 100, 1962 November 9 (Box 67, Folder 6-7)
- "Buccal Amylase and Clinical Studies" 4:93, Issue 101, 1962 November 23 (Box 67, Folder 8-9)
- "The Control of Urethral Catheter Infections" 4:94, Issue 101, 1962 November 23 (Box 67, Folder 10-12)
- "Hydralazine" 4:95, Issue 101, 1962 November 23 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
- "Office and Laboratory Tests for Choice of Antimicrobial Agents" 4:97, Issue 102, 1962 December 7 (Box 68, Folder 3-7)
- "Premenstrual Tension" 4:99, Issue 102, 1962 December 7 (Box 68, Folder 8-9)
- "Fallout and Countermeasures" 4:100, Issue 102, 1962 December 7 (Box 68, Folder 10-11, Box 69, Folder 1-2)
- "Aralen, Plaquenil, and Retinopathy" 4:103, Issue 103, 1962 December 21 (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
- "Aldactone and Aldactone-A" 4:104, Issue 103, 1962 December 21 (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
- "Caution Regarding Podophyllum" 4:106, Issue 103, 1962 December 21 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- "Acetaminophen, Phenacetic and Asprin" 5:7, Issue 105, 1963 January 18 (Box 69, Folder 8-10)
- "Ampicillin and Other Penicillins" 5:9, Issue 106, 1963 February 1 (Box 69, Folder 11, Box 70, Folder 1)
- "Antabuse" 5:12, Issue 106, 1963 February 1 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- "Hydromax" 5:14, Issue 107, 1963 February 15 (Box 70, Folder 3-4)
- "L-Glutavite [Sources, Reprints]" 5:23, Issue 109, 1963 March 15; 2 of 2 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- "Sonilyn" 5:26, Issue 110, 1963 March 29 (Box 70, Folder 6-7)
- "Anergex" 5:28, Issue 110, 1963 March 29 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- "Drugs to Curb the Tobacco Habit" 5:37, Issue 113, 1963 May 10 (Box 70, Folder 9-11)
- "Rauwolfia Alkaloids as Tranquilizing and Antihypertensive Drugs" 5:39, Issue 113, 1963 May 10 (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
- "Rhulihist, Antihistamines and Poison Ivy" 5:42, Issue 114, 1963 May 24 (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
- "Thiosulfil and Mesulfin" 5:43, Issue 114, 1963 May 24 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents note
  {Note "Drugs Infl. Sexual Desire & Performance" 5:45 in Box 156}.
- "Old Drugs - New Hazards, I. Tetracylines" 5:47, Issue 115, 1963 June 7 (Box 71, Folder 8-9)
- "Old Drugs - New Hazards, II. Vitamin K Supplements in Pregnancy and Labor" 5:47, Issue 115, 1963 June 7 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- "Tocosamine" 5:59, Issue 118, 1963 July 19 (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
- "Intrinsic Factor in Pernicious Anemia" 5:60, Issue 118, 1963 July 19 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- "Phenindione - A Hazardous Anticoagulant" 5:63, Issue 119, 1963 August 2 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- "Papase" 5:65, Issue 120, 1963 August 16 (Box 72, Folder 3-4)
- "Papase" 5:65, Issue 120, 1973 February 22; 3 of 3 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- "Proketazine, a New Antipsychotic Drug" 5:66, Issue 120, 1963 August 16 (Box 72, Folder 6-7)
- "Thyroid, Thyroxine and Triiodothryoxine" 5:69, Issue 121, 1963 August 30 (Box 72, Folder 8-13, Box 73, Folder 1)
- "Trivalent Live-Virus Oral Polio Caccine" 5:72, Issue 121, 1963 August 30 (Box 73, Folder 2-3)
- "Urinary LDH as a Test for Cancer" 5:76, Issue 122, 1964 September 13 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- "Interpretation of Bacteriuria" 5:82, Issue 124, 1963 October 11 (Box 73, Folder 5-6)
- "Parnate - A Warning" 5:88, Issue 125, 1963 October 25 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- "Drugs for Parasitic Infections" 5:89, Issue 126, 1963 November 8 (Box 73, Folder 8-11, Box 74, Folder 1-7)
- "Saccharin and Cyclamate" 5:96, Issue 127, 1963 November 22 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- "Uses and Hazards of Vitamin K Drugs" 5:97, Issue 128, 1963 December 6 (Box 74, Folder 9-11, Box 75, Folder 1)
- "IDU: An Antiviral Drug for Herpetic Eye Infections" 5:103, Issue 129, 1963 December 20 (Box 75, Folder 2-3)
- "Anergex" 5:104, Issue 129, 1963 December 20 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- "Treatment of Pulmonary Insufficiency" 6:1, Issue 130, 1964 January 3 (Box 75, Folder 5-10)
- "New Drug Offerings" 6:7, Issue 131, 1964 January 17 (Box 75, Folder 11-12)
- "Salicylamide" 6:14, Issue 133, 1964 February 14 (Box 76, Folder 1-3)
- "Valium" 6:17, Issue 134, 1964 February 28 (Box 76, Folder 4-7)
- "Bristol's Tetrex and Other Tetracyclines" 6:18, Issue 134, 1964 February 28 (Box 76, Folder 8-9)
- "Vasodilator Drugs and Peripheral Vascular Disorders" 6:21, Issue 135, 1964 March 13 (Box 76, Folder 10-12, Box 77, Folder 1-3)
- "Ampicillin" 6:25, Issue 136, 1964 March 27 (Box 77, Folder 4-6)
- "'Uroscreen' and Urinary Tract Infections" 6:33, Issue 138, 1973 October 26 (Box 77, Folder 7-8)
- "Monilial and 'Nonspecific' Vaginitis" 6:34, Issue 138, 1964 April 24 (Box 77, Folder 9-11)
- "Transplantation of Organs" 6:36, Issue 138, 1964 April 24 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- "Anhydron - Another Thiazide Diuretic" 6:37, Issue 139, 1964 May 8 (Box 78, Folder 2-4)
- "Prostall for the Prostrate" 6:40, Issue 139, 1964 May 8 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- "Choice of Drugs for Emotional Disorders" 6:45, Issue 141, 1964 June 5 (Box 78, Folder 6-7)
- "Tempra and the Medical Letter" 6:48, Issue 141, 1964 June 5 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- "The Cost of Tetracycline Drugs" 6:51, Issue 142, 1964 June 19 (Box 78, Folder 9-11)
- "Signemycin" 6:53, Issue 143, 1964 July 3 (Box 78, Folder 12-13)
- "Corticosteroids, Antimetabolites and Other Drugs in the Treatment of Psoriasis" 6:54, Issue 143, 1964 July 3 (Box 79, Folder 1-3)
- "Staphylcoccal Enterocolitis" 6:61, Issue 145, 1964 July 31 (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
- "Hypoglycemia Resulting from Interaction of Drugs" 6:62, Issue 145, 1964 July 31 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- "Triosorb and Other T3 Uptake Tests for Thyroid Function" 6:67, Issue 146, 1964 August 14 (Box 79, Folder 7-8)
- "Drug Hazards in Anesthesia and Surgery" 6:67, Issue 146, 1964 August 14 (Box 79, Folder 9-11)
- "Artificial Sweeteners Again" 6:73, Issue 148, 1964 September 11 (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
- "Influenza Vaccine" 6:75, Issue 148, 1964 September 11 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- "Phenacetin" 6:79, Issue 149, 1964 September 25 (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
- "How Useful Are 'Broad-Spectrum' Antibiotics" 6:85, Issue 151, 1964 October 23 (Box 80, Folder 7-9)
- "Benzocaine" 6:86, Issue 151, 1964 October 23 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- "Control of Pain and Anziety During Diagnostic Procedures" 6:87, Issue 151, 1964 October 23 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- "Iodophor Antiseptics" 6:89, Issue 152, 1964 November 6 (Box 81, Folder 1-5)
- "Folic Acid Deficiency in Pregnancy" 6:90, Issue 152, 1964 November 6 (Box 81, Folder 6-7)
- "Drugs and Other Measures in the Treatment of Shock" 6:91, Issue 152, 1964 November 6 (Box 81, Folder 8-10)
- "Dextrostix" 6:93, Issue 153, 1964 November 20 (Box 81, Folder 11-12)
- "Treatment of Common Bacterial Meningitides" 6:94, Issue 153, 1964 November 20 (Box 81, Folder 13, Box 82, Folder 1-2)
- "Drugs for Hypertensive Crises" 6:97, Issue 154, 1964 December 4 (Box 82, Folder 3-6)
- "A Note on Fluphenazine and Other Phenothiazines" 6:99, Issue 154, 1964 December 4 (Box 82, Folder 7-9)
- "Phenylbutazone and Acute Leukemia" 6:100, Issue 154 (Box 82, Folder 10-11)
- "Phenothiazines, Barbituates and Narcotics in Preanesthetic Medication" 6:101, Issue 155, 1964 December 18 (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
- "Drugs and Other Therapies for Thermal Burns" 6:102, Issue 155, 1964 December 18 (Box 83, Folder 5-6)
- "Aminopyrine and Dipyrone" 6:104, Issue 155, 1964 December 18 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- The Medical Letter Volumes 1-6, 1959-1964 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- "DBI" 7:1, Issue 156, 1965 January 1 (Box 83, Folder 9-10)
- "Bile Acids and Extracts" 7:2, Issue 156, 1965 January 1 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
- "Drug Dosage for Infants and Children" 7:3, Issue 156, January 1, 1965 "Estimation of Dosage for the Elderly" 7:8, Issue 157, January 15, 1965, 1965 January 15 (Box 84, Folder 4-6)
- "Provest" 7:5, Issue 157, 1965 January 15 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- "Cephalothin (Keflin) " 7:6, Issue 157, 1965 January 15 (Box 84, Folder 8-10)
- "Chloroquine (Aralen) and Fetal Injury" 7:9, Issue 158, 1965 January 29 (Box 84, Folder 11-12)
- "The Effect of Excretion on Dosage and Toxicity of Antimicrobial Agents" 7:10, Issue 158, 1964 January 29 (Box 85, Folder 1-3)
- "Human Antitoxin in Prophylaxis and Treatment of Tetanus" 7:13, Issue 159, 1965 February 12 (Box 85, Folder 4-5)
- "Birtheez" 7:15, Issue 159, 1965 February 12 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- "Drugs for Gastrointestinal Flatulence" 7:15, Issue 159, 1965 February 12 (Box 85, Folder 7-9)
- "Dyrenium - A New Oral Diuretic Agent" 7:17, Issue 160, 1965 February 26 (Box 85, Folder 10-11)
- "Chlorpheniramine Maleate Tablets" 7:18, Issue 160, February 26, 1965 "Chlorpheniramine Maleate - A Correction" 7:28, Issue 162, March 26, 1965, 1965 February 26 1965 March 26 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- "Metrazol and Other Drugs in Emotional Disorders of Old Age" 7:19, Issue 160, 1965 February 26 (Box 86, Folder 2-3)
- "Staphylococcal 'Lysates' and Vaccines" 7:21, Issue 161, 1965 March 12 (Box 86, Folder 4-9)